Allen Goh, Software Developer

https://github.com/allengoh, 07403479757, allengoh13@gmail.com

PROFILE

A driven and highly motivated full-stack software developer who is experienced working with Ruby, RSpec, Sinatra, JavaScript, React Native, Expo Go, Express, Jest, Mongoose, PostgreSQL, and MongoDB.

A detail-oriented pharmacist currently practising in the UK since 2016, demonstrated empathetic and focused leadership leading an NHS COVID-19 vaccination team during the COVID-19 pandemic.

TECH PROJECTS

Divvy

https://github.com/allengoh/divvy-app

A mobile app for splitting the bill amongst friends and family in restaurants. Users can take a photo of a restaurant receipt and have it itemised on the app. It is able to add a few charges including tips, service charges, taxes, and able to subtract discounts.

Acebook

https://github.com/allengoh/the-axylotls-acebook

A social media web application for connecting with people. Users can sign up for an account with a profile, be able to upload a profile picture, view and comment on their friends posts, and give a like emoji on both posts and comments.

Bank-Tech-Test

https://github.com/allengoh/Bank-Tech-Test-Javascript

A terminal-based application for managing a bank account. Users can deposit money, withdraw money and print a bank statement listing the transactions and their dates.

EXPERIENCE

Jun 2022 — Oct 2022

Software Development, Makers Academy

London

- A recent Makers Academy software development boot camp graduate that teaches OOP, TDD, MVC, and SOLID principles in developing software.
- Collaborated with an Agile team to develop a restaurant bill-splitting app from scratch for the final project, emphasising pair programming, XP values, CI/CD and GitHub collaboration.

Jan 2018 — Present

Locum Pharmacist, Self employed

North East England

- Oversees the day-to-day operation of the pharmacy and complies with laws and regulations.
- Supply and calculate dosages of medicines ensuring they are safe and appropriate for every patient.
- Strive to achieve pharmacy business targets and increase revenue by providing NHS and private healthcare services such as vaccinations, medication reviews, etc.
- Provide counselling to patients regarding medications and minor ailments.

Jan 2021 — Sep 2021

Clinical Lead - NHS COVID-19 Vaccination Site, Fairfield Pharmacy and Acklam Road Pharmacy

Teesside area

- Led a COVID-19 vaccination team of 20 people in two pharmacies, achieved more than 60000 vaccinations completed since service started.
- Ensured the vaccination team was up to date with the latest NHS guidelines and knowledge of the vaccines.
- Clinically screened patients for vaccine eligibity and contraindications.
- Managed time off and sickness within the team and organised the workload on hand.
- Liaised with the local NHS vaccination support centre for vaccine supply and allocation.
- Addressed concerns and complaints from the patients and the public.

EDUCATION

Jan 2018 — Present

Chartered Financial Analyst (CFA®) Program participant

- Completed Level 1 in 2018
- Completed Level 2 in 2021

Sep 2010 — Jun 2014

Masters of Pharmacy, University of Sunderland

Sunderland

• Graduated with Upper Second-Class Honours (2:1)